Guide to the Tyree Scott Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- NORTHWEST LABOR AND EMPLOYMENT LAW OFFICE (LABOR AND EMPLOYMENT LAW OFFICE) RECORDS, 1961-2005; SERIES 10 (Box-folder 16/32-45/15)
  - Case Files and Legal Papers, 1961-1995; Subseries C (Box-folder 18/33-45/15)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Apprenticeship Program, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 25/19)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., General Planning, 1974 (Box-folder 25/20)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Ed Lontz, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 25/21)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., O-CF Joinder Motion, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 25/22)
    - Yates v. Metaclad Insulation, Discovery Notes, 1979 (Box-folder 25/23)
    - Local 7 Rule 19 Joinder Opposition Brief Work, 1976 (Box-folder 25/24)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Seattle King County Plan, 1979 (Box-folder 25/25)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., brand-Parsons Notice mailing, 1980 (Box-folder 25/26)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Pretrial Exhibits 250-272, circa 1970s and 1980s (Box-folder 25/27)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Pretrial Exhibits 250-272, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 25/28)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Marc Rosenblum Testimony, 1979 (Box-folder 25/29)
    - Farell E. Bloch- Possibly Resume, 1979 (Box-folder 25/30)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Documents Produced by Local 7 Former Tests, 1974 (Box-folder 25/31)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Pretrial Order Exhibits no. 249-255, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 25/32)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Labor Market Area, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 25/33)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Labor Market Area, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 25/34)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Seattle School District I, 1979 (Box-folder 25/35)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Discovery of Absent Class Members, 1977 (Box-folder 25/36)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Local 7 Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box-folder 25/37)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Dispatch Book, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 25/38)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., S.1292 (b) Appeals, 1959-1966 (Box-folder 25/39)
    - Memos of Intent Under Section 1981, Section 1985 & Section 703 (h), 1978 (Box-folder 25/40)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Local 302 (Yates, Buford & Aguillar - Jesse, Jerry Rye), 1979 (Box-folder 25/41)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Oral Argument File (Class Issue), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 25/42)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Documents Relating to Affirmative Action, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 25/43)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Apprenticeship Rotation, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 25/44)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Pre-Trial Order Exhibits 201-219, Contains the Constitution and By-Laws of the International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 25/45)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Pre-Trial Order Exhibits 63-100, Washington Contracts, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 25/46)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Pre-Trial Order Exhibits 280-293, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 25/47)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Pre-Trial Order Exhibits 181-200, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 26/1)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Local 7 Minutes--Body & Executive Board, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 26/2)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Pre-Trial Order Exhibits 256-279, 1972 (Box-folder 26/3)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Western Insulation Contractors Association (WICA) Minutes, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 26/4)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Joint Apprenticeship Committee (JAC) Trust Agreement, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 26/5)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Duplicate Minutes (JAC & WICA), Joint Apprenticeship Committee Western Insulation Contractors Association, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 26/6)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Joint Apprenticeship Committee (JAC) Minutes, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 26/7)
    - Bankruptcy and Back Pay Recovery, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 26/8)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 26/9)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Correspondence, 1961-1973 (Box-folder 26/10)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Duplicate Correspondence, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 26/11)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Pre-Trial Order Exhibits 1-61, 1968-1976 (Box-folder 26/12)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Miscellaneous Documents, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 26/13)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Pre-Trial Order- New Exhibits, 1979 (Box-folder 26/14)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Pre-Trial Order- Exhibits Copies 220-248, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 26/15)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Pre-Trial Order Exhibits (Extras), 1971-1975 (Box-folder 26/16)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Pre-Trial Order Exhibits (Extras), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 26/17)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Pre Job Conferences, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 26/18)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Protective Order Motions, 1972 (Box-folder 26/19)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Documents from U.S. Apprentice and Training Bureau, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 26/20)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Equal Employment Opportunity Committee (EEOC) Reports, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 26/21)
    - Brown v. Joint Apprenticeship Committee (JAC), Application Log Book, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 26/22)
    - Brown v. Joint Apprenticeship Committee (JAC), Application Log Book, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 26/23)
    - Brown v. Joint Apprenticeship Committee (JAC) Documents Produced by Defendant. Women Interested in Construction Electrician Apprenticeship, 1977 (Box-folder 26/24)
    - Unlabeled File, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) National Apprenticeship and Training Standards- for Industrial Applications, 1971 (Box-folder 26/25)
    - Brown v. Joint Apprenticeship Committee (JAC) Deposition Notes, 1978 (Box-folder 26/26)
    - Brown v. Joint Apprenticeship Committee (JAC) Documents Produced by Defendant, Equal Employment Opportunity Apprenticeship Information Report, 1970 (Box-folder 26/27)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Misc. unfoldered Document, 1978 (Box-folder 26/28)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Correspondence, 1978 (Box-folder 26/29)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., NEFCO Payroll Register, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 26/30)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Fisherman Issue, 1976 (Box-folder 26/31)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO), NEFCO Application Log, 1976 (Box-folder 26/32)
    - New England Fish Company (NEFCO) Interrogatories Collated, 1974 (Box-folder 26/33)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Alaska Packers Association [Re Claim of Sam Cabansag], 1979 (Box-folder 27/1)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Alaska Shell, 1979 (Box-folder 27/2)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Arthur E. Berthelsen, 1976 (Box-folder 27/3)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of William H. Backman, 1976 (Box-folder 27/4)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Jose Bartolo, 1976 (Box-folder 27/5)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Boeing Company, 1979 (Box-folder 27/6)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Tom Benson, 1976 (Box-folder 27/7)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Richard Byington, 1976 (Box-folder 27/8)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition upon Oral Examination of Constantine Baruso, 1976 (Box-folder 27/9)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Hugh Carr, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 27/10)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Hugh Carr, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 27/11)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Sam Cabansag Jr. (1 of 2), 1975 (Box-folder 27/12)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Sam Cabansag Jr. (2 of 2), 1975 (Box-folder 27/13)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Beverly J. Barnes, 1979 (Box-folder 27/14)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Michael Cervantes, 1974 (Box-folder 27/15)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Patrick Chestnutt, 1976 (Box-folder 27/16)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Jesus B. Condes Jr., 1976 (Box-folder 27/17)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of John M. DeHoogh, 1976 (Box-folder 27/18)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Tony Diaz, 1976 (Box-folder 27/19)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Gilbert Edelman, 1976 (Box-folder 27/20)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Tauno Freeman, 1976 (Box-folder 27/21)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Leonard Frandsen, 1976 (Box-folder 27/22)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Arnold Gibson, 1976 (Box-folder 27/23)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Henry Gunderson (II), 1975 (Box-folder 27/24)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Henry Gunderson, 1976 (Box-folder 27/25)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Jay Gage (Exhibits), 1970-1971 (Box-folder 27/26)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Anthony Gregory, 1976 (Box-folder 27/27)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Jay S. Gage (II), 1976 (Box-folder 27/28)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Jay Gage Continued (III + IV), 1976 (Box-folder 27/29)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Exhibits to Arnold Gibson Deposition, 1976 (Box-folder 27/30)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Exhibits to Arnold Gibson Deposition, 1976 (Box-folder 27/31)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Robert Hirstel., 1976 (Box-folder 27/32)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Charles K. Hoines, 1976 (Box-folder 27/33)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Henry Helm, 1979 (Box-folder 28/1)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Exhibit from James Jacobsen Deposition, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 28/2)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of James Jacobsen, 1974 (Box-folder 28/3)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of James Jacobsen, 1976 (Box-folder 28/4)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of David Jessup, 1976 (Box-folder 28/5)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Norman Johnson, 1976 (Box-folder 28/6)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Loren Kondo, 1976 (Box-folder 28/7)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Nellie Kookesh, 1975 (Box-folder 28/8)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Nellie Kookesh, 1975 (Box-folder 28/9)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of John Lyon, 1976 (Box-folder 28/10)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Libby McNeill, 1979 (Box-folder 28/11)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of William McGrath, 1976 (Box-folder 28/12)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Agrippina Merculief, 1975 (Box-folder 28/13)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Donald Mayall, 1976 (Box-folder 28/14)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Audrey Merculief, 1975 (Box-folder 28/15)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of North Seattle Community College, 1979 (Box-folder 28/16)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Feliz Narte, 1976 (Box-folder 28/17)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Dan Nielson, 1976 (Box-folder 28/18)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Patrick O'Leary, 1976 (Box-folder 28/19)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Mary Paul, 1975 (Box-folder 28/20)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Charles Perkins, 1975 (Box-folder 28/21)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Purged Deposition of Doug Peralta, 1976 (Box-folder 28/22)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of the Portland School District, circa 1970s (Box-folder 28/23)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Pacific NW Bell, 1979 (Box-folder 28/24)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of W.A. Peterson, 1976 (Box-folder 28/25)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of C. Reed Rogers, 1976 (Box-folder 28/26)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Renton Vocational, 1979 (Box-folder 28/27)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Ted Ranjo, 1976 (Box-folder 28/28)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Marvin Remlinger, 1976 (Box-folder 28/29)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Ralph Robinson, 1976 (Box-folder 28/30)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Ingevald Ronnestad, 1976 (Box-folder 28/31)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Pete Sotello, 1976 (Box-folder 28/32)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of John Sagli Part 1 of 2, 1976 (Box-folder 28/33)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of John Sagli Part 2 of 2, 1976 (Box-folder 28/34)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Thomas Sullivan, 1976 (Box-folder 28/35)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Raymond Spindle, 1976 (Box-folder 29/1)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Samuel Strauss, 1975 (Box-folder 29/2)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of George Sovik, 1976 (Box-folder 29/3)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Seattle School District, 1979 (Box-folder 29/4)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Seattle School District Number 1, 1979 (Box-folder 29/5)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Seattle Central Community College, 1979 (Box-folder 29/6)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Seattle Prep High School, 1979 (Box-folder 29/7)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Harold Thom, 1975 (Box-folder 29/8)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Harold Thom Continued, 1976 (Box-folder 29/9)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of University of Washington, 1979 (Box-folder 29/10)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of John Webby, 1976 (Box-folder 29/11)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Deposition of Richard Marvin, 1979 (Box-folder 29/12)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Interviews and Factual Background, 1968-1976 (Box-folder 29/13)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Employee Form Letters, circa 1970s (Box-folder 29/14)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Nicanor Managan-Witness File, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 29/15)
    - New England Fish Company (NEFCO)- Job Announcements and Ads, 1978 (Box-folder 29/16)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Bogle & Gates, 1977 (Box-folder 29/17)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., NEFCO Prints (Uganik, Pederson Point), 1981 (Box-folder 29/18)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Discovery Working File, circa 1970s (Box-folder 29/19)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Writ of Mandamus, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 29/20)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Relief Stage- Hearing, 1977 (Box-folder 29/21)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Relief Stage- Damages Research, Undated (Box-folder 29/22)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Relief Stage-Appointment of Monitor, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 29/23)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Hearing, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 29/24)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Relief Stage- Proposed Order on Injunctive Relief, 1977 (Box-folder 29/25)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Relief Stage- Reply to NEFCO's Supplemental Briefs, Undated (Box-folder 29/26)
    - Cannery Cases-General Joinder of Unions Issue, 1976 (Box-folder 29/27)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Hearing, 1978 (Box-folder 29/28)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Facts on Housing Damages, Undated (Box-folder 29/29)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Memo on Defining Vacancies, Undated (Box-folder 29/30)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Relief Stage- Local Rule CR 23 Motion, 1977 (Box-folder 29/31)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Appealability of Liability Ruling on Messing, Undated (Box-folder 29/32)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Relief Stage- Documents, 1967-1975 (Box-folder 29/33)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Retroactive Back Pay Limitation- Frobig v. Held, Undated (Box-folder 29/34)
    - Testimony of Nemesio Domingo Jr.- U.S. Comm. On Civil Rights, 1981 (Box-folder 29/35)
    - New England Fish Company (NEFCO)- Housing, circa 1970s (Box-folder 29/36)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Relief Stage- Injunctive Relief, 1978 (Box-folder 29/37)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Terminated Employees, 1976 (Box-folder 29/38)
    - Cannery Cases-General Department of Interior Files Part 1 of 2, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 29/39)
    - Cannery Cases-General Department of Interior Files Part 2 of 2, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 29/40)
    - Cannery Cases- More General Department of Interior Files, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 29/41)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Laurel Bland Study, 1975 (Box-folder 29/42)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Documents Produced- Hiring for tender jobs, 1973 (Box-folder 29/43)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., More Documents Produced, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 29/44)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Temporary Document File, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 29/45)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al., Exhibits- Cannery Chart of Accounts, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 29/46)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Miscellaneous Documents- Shipped Egegik and Pederson Point Part 1 of 2, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 29/47)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Miscellaneous Documents- Shipped Egegik and Pederson Point Part 2 of 2, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 29/48)